<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">AndroidGuide</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_activity2">Terminology</string>
    <string name="term">Terminology</string>
    <string name="web">WebSties</string>
    <string name="help">help</string>
    <string name="about">about</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_activity3">WebSites</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_activity4">Help</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_activity5">About</string>
    <string name="name">YunJeong,Heo</string>
    <string name="prog">Computer Programming Analysis</string>
    <string name="desterm">The terminology button allows you to link to the page which is to research the
    terminology of android studio from lab1 and lab2</string>
    <string name="desweb">The websites button allows you to go to the android tutorial websites directly.</string>
    <string name="instruct_term">Enter the terminology of android studio.</string>
    <string name="instruct_web">Click on one of the following links</string>

    <string-array name="list_of_terminology">
        <item>Android Debug Bridge</item>
        <item>Emulator</item>
        <item>Screen shot2</item>
        <item>Gradle</item>
        <item>pm</item>
        <item>Lint</item>
        <item>Project</item>
        <item>Panel</item>
        <item>toolbar</item>
        <item>status bar</item>
        <item>preview pane</item>
        <item>android pane</item>
        <item>project explorer</item>
        <item>.idea folder</item>
        <item>intelligence</item>
        <item>module</item>
        <item>live layout</item>
        <item>init</item>
        <item>commit</item>
        <item>push</item>
        <item>add</item>
        <item>pull</item>
        <item>branch</item>
        <item>clone</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="terminology_array">
        <item>Android Debug Bridge communicates with an emulator, for example using "adb install" command, it connects to client
	which runs on your development machine, and a shell is the place to communicate between clients and devices.</item>
        <item>Lint is a tool which finds errors in your codes and explain the problems, such as perfomence, usability and version
	compatibility. "gradle lint" command creates a lint report.</item>
        <item>Emulator is a virtual mobile device, you can test and run  applications without using actual physical devices.
	For example "emulator adv name of your VD t (target) b(binary interface)" is a command for creating virtual devices.</item>
        <item>Screen shot2 is a program creating image sources; it takes a picture like camera does, so you can make a image of your
	current window or current works on the screen.</item>
        <item>Gradle is a build tool which can customize your projects. it allows you to use command line and to build your own
	applications from Androids studio. For example ,you can set up various versions or configuration of your projects,
	in "build.gradle" file.</item>
        <item>pm is a command to manage  android packages within an adb shell. It allows you to delete packages and to list
	packages installed on your device. </item>
        <item>project is the current work in progress, as well as the final program.It is the application that the developer wants to create.</item>
        <item>Panel presents the devices and view of your application output. You can adjust images or layout
		esliy without considering coding for measuring each android device models screen sizes, types.</item>
         <item>toolbar, Android studio allows to use customizable toolbar which you can access tools easily, such as saving,
  		opening, synchronizing files, undoing, redoing the previous actions, running application and creating VM directly etc.</item>
        <item>status bar, It shows the current running process information, such as encoding format of the file and corresponding messages for changed activities.</item>
        <item>Preview pane allows you to preview the layout on devices on the right side of the window when
 		you are editing in the text view. You can modify layout theme and look at different device skins.</item>
        <item>android pane, Each Android Models has different sizes and types.the pane allows to display multiple views. There are two types of pane in Android,
		single pane is only able to show another view on separated window, but the previous view still is running on background.
		Muilti pane is able to show another view and current view on the same window.</item>
        <item>project explorer gives an overview of the project and allows the user to see the basic details, and can be used to organize and color
            code different folders and files within the project.</item>
        <item>.idea folder contains a set of configuration files. For example, compiler.xml, encoding.xml, and moduls.xml contains
 		configuration information, such as names and locations, compiler seeing and its component modules.</item>
        <item>intelligence, this feature helps to speed up development by minimizing the mount of memorization required from the programmer,
            and reducing the number of key strokes. It also minimizes errors or types and other mistakes. It is a form of auto completion,
		 like the auto correct on a smart phone keyboard.</item>
        <item>Module is a component of an application. Each modules has an individual function which can build, test, and
		debug independently.</item>
        <item>Live layout allows you to preview at the same time when you edit text or xml layout without running emulator or
                on devices.</item>
        <item>init, Initializes a git repository and creates the initial ".git" directory in a new or in an existing project.</item>
        <item>commit, Takes all of the changes written in the index, creates a new commit object pointing to it and allows the user to add a note or an explanation. </item>
        <item>push, Updates the modified local objects to the remote repository.</item>
        <item>add, Adds files changes or contents in your working directory to your index.</item>
        <item>pull, Fetches the files from the remote repository or merges it with your local branch. </item>
        <item>branch, Lists existing branches. Creates a new branch if a branch name is provided. Deletes existing branches. </item>
        <item>clone, Make a repository copy from a remote source into new directory. </item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="weblist_array">
        <item>http://developer.android.com</item>
        <item>http://www.codelearn.org</item>
        <item>http://www.vogella.com</item>
        <item>http://androidituts.com</item>
        <item>http://www.mkyong.com</item>
        <item>http://www.javatpoint.com</item>
        <item>http://www.tutorialspoint.com</item>
        <item>http://www.androidaspect.com</item>
        <item>http://developer.xamarin.com</item>
        <item>http://androidituts.com</item>
        <item>http://tutorials.jenkov.com</item>
        <item>http://www.sitepoint.com</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
